LAITH ABU FADDA



Full Stack Web Developer (ReactJS | NodeJS | NextJS | MongoDB)

PERSONAL DETAILS

Amman laithfadda4@gmail.com, +962 771101109 Website: laith-portfolio.vercel.app LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/laith-abu-fadda

PROFILE

I am a highly skilled Full Stack Web Developer with a Bachelor's degree in Computer and Information Systems. I have a strong background in debugging, web application development, and full-stack web developer coding. My technical skills include proficiency in Tailwind CSS, Mongodb compass, Postman API, HTML, Redux.js, REST APIs, and testing. I also have experience in project management, Agile methodologies, and problem-solving. I am fluent in English, have excellent communication skills, and excel in teamwork. My expertise includes React.js, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Bootstrap, and NextJS.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree, Computer and Information Systems Security/Information Assurance

University of Jordan

Jan 2019 - Dec 2023

EMPLOYMENT

Full Stack web Developer Dec 2023 - Present

Tajseer

Full stack web Developer Oct 2023 - Dec 2023

Arrab Consulting (ARRC)

SKILLS

React.js Node.js

NextJS Nest.js

Redux.js Express.js

MongoDB REST APIs

Typescript Debugging

Web Application Development Front-end Coding

This resume is made with CVwizard.com.

Tailwind CSS Mongodb compass

Postman API HTML

Testing Project Management

Communication Agile Methodologies

Problem Solving Time Management

Teamwork Bootstrap (Framework)

INTERNSHIPS

Software engineer Sep 2023 - Oct 2023

Estarta, Amman

CERTIFICATES

• Coding School Certificate-orange

- Modern React with Redux [2023 Update] (Udemy)
- front End Web Development | Ultimate Guide (Udemy)
- Full Stack Web Development: Node Express MongoDB (Udemy)
- Node.js: The Complete Guide to Build RESTful APIs (Udemy)
- MongoDB The Complete Developers Guide
- JavaScript Data Structures & Algorithms (Udemy)
- Node.js API Masterclass With Express & MongoDB
- The Ultimate React Course 2024: React, Next.js, Redux & More
- Next.js 14 & React The Complete Guide
- Nest js typescript

PROJECTS

- Jobify Website
- Events-Managment-System-JU
- mern food website
- Notaty Website
- QuickN websit
- Brainwave
- X clone
- Music composer website
- Admin dashboard website
- LMS website
- pros shop E-commerce
- Blog website (nextjs)
- Bootcamp apis
- Booking website
- imdb clone

REFERENCES

References available upon request.